As I said, I'm going to download
the index of the intermodular project.
Uh, okay.  And now I want to
download it.  Now,
okay?  What I'm showing you
is, as I said, the rules for this
course
on how to approach the
intermodular project,
and we're going to adhere to the
rules, obviously.  So for
that, so for that, uh, let's see
the point they give us, that is, let's
see uh what we have to do.
So, look for information
on typical companies on the Internet.  I'm going to write all
this down,
okay?  I'm going to point all this out because I'm already
telling you that it is the norm.
Hey, new folder.  Wait, I'm going to do it
here, I'm almost going to finish sooner.
HTML
and so on, so let's see what
the subject has.  First project
really put interdisciplinary is
intermodular.
Intermodular.
Okay.  Intermodular project.  Point
number one, search
for information.
Okay, point number two, selecting a
service.
Selection of a service or product.
Point number three.
003,
uh,
spinoff company proposal.
Point number four,
it relates to the
relationship of the business unit.
Point number five, transmit
information,
okay?
Transmission of information.
And to create one or more modules,
okay?  Information search,
company characterization, all of this,
okay?  There are going to be a series of points.
Let's see, these are the
learning outcomes and
assessment criteria here.  And this down here is the
evaluation criteria.  Okay,
characterize.  Let's make sure it
's the same.
Well, let's go down here, shall we?
001,
identify
representative companies.
002 company structure 003
characteristics
of departments.
004 functions of each department.
005.
Oh, let's
see, here.
Okay, this is
005.
Business volume assessment
006.
Strategy
to respond to demands.  In terms of
business volume, I can tell you that we
are going to do the project on
artificial intelligence.  But why?
Because the instructions themselves tell us so
.  I mean,
artificial intelligence AI.
Okay, IA.  Not this.
and to space.
Well, it'll be around there, okay?  But
there is a guideline which is the use of
artificial intelligence in the
development of the project.  Eh, strategy
to respond.  Assessment
007, assessment of human,
human and material resources.
Uh,
realization
008,
follow-up realization
and we're going to see
sustainable development.
Okay,
from here on in point 002
identify,
we have to identify the
market needs.
002 propose possible solutions.  I'd like to take this
opportunity to tell you that the
Ministry's own instructions
indicate that teamwork should be encouraged and fostered
.
I'm going to skip that, I'm telling you now.
Okay, so all the projects you do are going to
be, hey, by the way, I'm not watching
the chat, okay?  All the projects
you do are going to be individual.  So,
Sandro, you asked a moment ago,
what is this subject for?  This
course serves not only to teach you how to
program, but also to teach you how to
propose a project, okay?  how to
analyze the market, detect a
need that the market has and
propose a project that meets that
need and therefore serves
people.  Let's continue with the
agenda and then we'll see,
well, propose possible solutions,
okay?  eh in a group, right?  information
[Music]
relating to innovative solutions
and
aspects.
Technical feasibility study,
project components,
necessary human and material resources,
economic budget 008,
preparation of economic budgets
009, design documentation,
and related aspects
of project quality
and public presentation.
public presentation
of the most relevant ideas.
Okay, three.  Point three,
planning the execution,
timing
of the sequences of activities,
determination
of resources and logistics
for each activity.
What I'm doing, by the way, is
a micro-break.  These days you've
been asking me, "Hey, do you have a
folder structure?"  We
have to have the same structure
as you.  My answer, obligation, no.
Recommendation, of course.  Okay, you
see that the folders I have
correspond to what the
regulations indicate that we have to teach, which
then, obviously, this is what
the regulations indicate that we have to teach
as a minimum, okay?  And then obviously
we'll go beyond the minimum, okay?  But
the idea is that if I have it arranged this way
, it's not because I feel like it,
but because the regulations say that this
is the order of the contents that go into
this cycle.  That's why I
recommend that you organize your work in the same way I
do,
like doing the same thing
I'm doing, that is, creating
folders, okay?  So, we're at
number three, which is permits.
and
necessary authorizations.
four
eh activities
that involve risks
eh
occupational risk prevention plan 006
material and human resources
for each activity
possible
unforeseen events
necessary documentation
voucher number four
monitors
and 001
activity monitoring procedure.
verification
of the quality of the results of the
activities.
Identification
of possible
deviations
in planning
Information
on possible deviations.
solution and documentation of
deviations
definition
and preparation
of documentation,
okay?  And in point five,
which is to transmit information
clearly, 001 with an
orderly
and methodical attitude.
Let's see.
Uh,
horizontal and vertical transmission of information.
use of computer media
to transmit information
and technical terms
in other standard languages ​​of
the sector.
Okay, that's it.
Now that we've started talking about
this index, let's
talk about what this index is all about—that
is, what developing a
modular project involves.  To do this, here I'm
going to create, now I'm going to do it with
headit intermodular project 001001
and we're going to talk about it in the same way as
in any other subunit of
001 basic contents,
eh exercises
and 01
evaluation criteria.
Here in basic contents
I'm going to put 001 basic contents
md.
Here in exercises I'm not going to put anything and
here in criteria I'm going to put 001
evaluation criteriamd.
So
now
we are going to see the intermodular project.   I
'll copy this here and paste it into each
subject, sorry, into each subunit.
here.
And now we make a summary.
I'm going to do it in a Oh, damn it.   I
'm going to do it in a document.
And transmission of information.
Okay,
so what are we going
to do in this class and how are we going
to present it?  How are we going to approach the
projects?  First of all, as I
was saying, in intermodular projects, the
projects are not designed so that we
do one a year, okay?  but rather we should
do several small projects a
year, because in the first one we will do it badly
and then we will do it better and then we will
do it better and then we will do it better.
What is the objective?  The goal, once
again, as I was saying a little earlier in
development environments, is not to start
programming, okay?  But the first thing
we have to do is identify
representative companies.  Let's see.
Okay, the first thing we need to do
is analyze the market a little.
Wait and see if I can fold.
Come on, great.  First, we will look for
companies in the sector that develop the
same product that we want to
develop.  We will now analyze
these companies.  Years ago I was
largely involved in training and
developing video games.  So one
day a student comes, let's see, be careful
here, okay?  This is on it.  And he
says to me, "Hey, I want to do a
final project for myself."  At that time I was a
master's degree, eh, that it's a video game like
GTA V. And I said to him, "Look, if GTA V has
two people involved, I mean, two
people, 200 people, I meant, and it
took them 5 years to do it
and you say that you're only going to do it in
two months, it's not that I don't trust you,
okay? But I think you should analyze
what the structure of other companies
that have developed the same product that
you have developed
is to see what it takes to
develop a product like the one you
want to develop, okay? To have
a more realistic perspective of
what is needed, okay? Yes. No, thank
goodness he didn't tell me about GTA 6 because we
still don't know
the people who have
worked on GTA 6 because it's not
finished, or even the
release date that they keep delaying little by
little, or what it cost or anything.
We've seen Trailers, it looks very good
. You already know that there is controversy with the
supposed price that the game will have,
but we don't even know anything  You're welcome,
indeed. Okay, not in this case
so much applied to a game, but applied
to business software, which in the end is
software. I mean, in the end, a
video game is still a
commercial software product, that is, it
really is a perfectly
valid project. The only thing is that the
multimedia development subject, which
is where we see
video game development, is in the second year. That's why I'm not
telling you about making a video game in the
first year,
okay? What are the characteristics of the
departments in those companies? How many
people are there in programming? How many people are there
in administration? Maybe there's a
transportation and
logistics department. Why? Well, because maybe
if it's a company that manufactures software and
sells it in boxes, you might have to have
a small software shipping department
. I don't know. Okay? What
functions does each department perform? What
volume of business does what you're going to do have
? I mean, what volume of
business, what supply, what demand, okay?
What strategy are you going to have to
respond to demands?
What valuation? How many
material and human resources do you need?
How many  How many computers do you need? How many
employees do you need? If you need 30
employees, you can't fit them
all in one room; you'll have to
rent a space, but how much will
that space cost? Okay, so, finally,
activity monitoring. And you know that according to the
new regulations, it's important that
we take into account the sustainability of the
energy consumption of the software we
're going to develop, how it impacts the
environment, okay? These are things that
for a long time have seemed
silly, but they're not. Really, if you
think about it, if you stop to think about it, they
're not at all. And I also have
more and more students who are more concerned
about this issue, which I think is
great. It's not just that in second year you have
a new subject called
sustainability, but it's also
important that, not just because of the subject,
but on your own initiative, you take an
interest, okay? That's why
, well, selection of a service or
product, which is, in other words, look to see what
the market needs, identify
market needs, propose
possible solutions,
information related to  Those solutions,
how your application can be
innovative, a response with
artificial intelligence. Don't complicate things, okay?
Study that what you propose is
technically viable, that it can actually be
done.
It's like I'm going to make
augmented reality glasses on my own. And it's like,
uh, let's see, if
neither Google nor Apple are able to do that, why are
you going to make them? I mean, what do you
know that they don't know? What do you have that
they don't? Okay? What you
propose has to be viable. It's like
if you tell me, "I'm going to make the
Back to the Future hoverboard." Well,
I hope so, but let's see. Show me that
you can do it. What parts will
the project have? What do you need to
launch the project?
Uh, you'll have to make a
financial budget for how much that's going to cost.
Important documentation, okay? And
presentation. And then later on, a
proposal, okay? You already have a
product. Hey, so let's make a
company like that.  product, okay? Come on, you're
not going to make it yourself. I mean, each
one of you is going to make your own company.
What resources do you need? What permits do you
need for that company? If there are
risky activities, for example, if
at some point in that company
a computer needs to be assembled or disassembled, well, as I
said
before, in computer systems, that
's clearly a
risky activity, which isn't pointing, okay? It's
not like skydiving,
but if there's an activity that entails
risk, then there has to be an
occupational risk prevention plan to
ensure that no one is injured
or killed by the
start-up of that
business activity,
material and human resources, and then the
list of business units, okay?
How the units relate to each other
and the transmission of information between
business units. Okay? So,
what's the first thing we're going to do?
Okay, I'll tell you, just as
the regulations say, I insist once again,
okay? I refer to the regulations. In other words,
to a large extent what I do is
try  Deliver the content as it
should be delivered. Then we'll see the
difference between theory and
practice, but okay, eh, how do you
teach this subject?
Let's see, you have to design a series
of challenges. If they can be small
challenges, believe me, all the better, but for
you, okay? Not for me. Just a moment, I
'm going to drink.
Okay.
And for each challenge,
the challenge will have a context as
close to you as possible.
And this is the first important part of
the subject. I'm not going to choose the
challenges.
You're going to choose the challenges, okay?
Each one of you has to choose the
project you're working on.
In the rest of the subjects, I'm probably
going to give you little freedom because it's not
applied. If you have to learn to program, you have to
learn to program; there's no
freedom there. But in the project, each
one of you is going to set a challenge
that's close and real.
For example, a challenge wouldn't be, I'm going to
make Google by myself in the first
quarter of first year. Of course. Very well,
perfect. There we go. Okay, or  Well, I'm going to
make a Google, it's not a real challenge.
Now I'm going to make a software that fulfills
this objective. For example, a small
accounting software. That's a
real challenge. I
'm going to make a software through which
people can
recycle and people will enter
what they have to recycle and I will
inform them of the nearest recycling point.
That's a real challenge, okay? A software
that is in your hands. If you
tell me, "I'm going to make Microsoft and I'm going to
make an operating system in 3 months." It
's not real. I'm telling you now that it's not real.
Okay, now if you tell me, let's see,
well, I'm going to make an application
that destroys the operating system in
one click, that's real,
that's a very feasible application, but
importantly,
the application has to be something that
improves the world, okay? And destroying the
operating system with one click doesn't
improve the world, so that would be
feasible, but not operational, it would be
unacceptable, okay? Yes, but it's a challenge,
okay? But not a challenge from the point of view of
view of the intermodular project, if it's not
more of a personal challenge. Okay,
coordination with your classmates is important. I'm
going to skip this. The challenges are going to be
individual.
The challenge has to be
broad enough to allow for creativity in
the answers and be meaningful
to the students. Meaningful for the
students means that theoretically
I choose the challenge,
but it means something to
you, well, no. That's why you
choose the challenge, okay? And that way it will surely
mean something to you. It
must be designed to be solved
as a team. No, no, I'm going to
screw that up, I'll tell you now. And its design will be
aimed at facilitating the evaluation of
the learning outcomes.
Learning outcomes are what I
just put here. That is, the design
of the activity must be aimed at being
able to be solved using these steps
that I've put here, okay?
And that's it. So that's what we're going to
do over the next few months. In addition, you'll
also say, "Okay, this is good,
but how are we going to do it?"  to do?" Well,
every project we do will be like
this.
Every project we do
will use a little bit of
markup languages ​​for the user interface, for
the visible, for the pretty. Then
we'll use programming for the
operation, for the logic. The
first samples, I'll tell you now, I'm
going to do them, okay? I'm going to do them
and then from there you
will apply them, modify them and this will be
in the following weeks because do
n't worry, right now you still don't have
the basics to
even be able to do a mini project of
this, okay?
And that project will save data and for
that we will use the databases subject
.
And all of this will be framed in a
development environment and for that
we will use the development environments subject
. And the project you do
will run on a computer, on a
development team or on a server
which will be a computer system
and we will have to see what processor
the computer system has, what RAM, what
hard drive is necessary, what
operating system is needed and all that. Okay?
So basically, for  Just so you know,
this subject is about creating
small projects. Don't
worry, don't worry. For
now, I'm going to do the first—the first—
interdisciplinary project
, okay? That is, correct, Piero,
indeed, just as you just
mentioned, all the projects will have a
back and a front, where the front will be
done with markup languages ​​and the back
will be done with programming and
databases. Okay? So, I'm going
to do a project, I'm going to do an
information search, I'll analyze
companies, detect a need, I
'll start programming code, I'll propose
a company, okay? And I'll give you a
complete and phenomenal example.
And from there, once I
do it, while I do it,
the weeks will go by, and therefore we'll
get a head start on the rest of the
subjects. We'll learn a little bit
of programming and a little bit of
markup languages, and so by the time I do that,
by the time I finish it and tell you,
"Okay, now you've
seen enough content in the rest
of the subjects to be able to start
doing things and start to
isolate.
Okay.
And so.  So, eh,
well that's it, that's what it is.
So, so
nothing, today a little more of this
subject because you see that we can't
advance much more, so
eh I'm going to start, I'm going to start, okay, I'm going to
start because that's how we
eh make the most of our time, okay?
Because it's 4:30, we have time,
so we don't have to take a half-hour
break until the next class.  Let's
see,
let's see,
give me a second.   Let's
go there.
You see, I'm going to start, okay?
I insist, I'm going to start by doing the
project myself.  I want to do a project and
I know I want to do it on
artificial intelligence.  Because?
Because today, I'm not telling you that you
have to do it the same way as me, you can
do it the same way as me or you can do it
differently, okay?  But today I
know that what's really happening and what's going to
continue to happen is
artificial intelligence.  I know it.  So I say,
look, I'm going after that niche market,
but I have to be aware of
who I am.  Okay, we'll talk about the
Where is the issue of it being
technologically viable?  That is to say, I'm going to
suddenly found an open all by myself right now, right here
in my house.  Well no, it's
different, okay?  It's difficult.  What I have to
do is analyze what I can
do, what my market niche is,
what I can't do, and what I
can do.  What's more, look, I
'm going to tell you.  I'm going to turn on GPT and
say, uh, what investment in hardware,
uh, human resources and
uh economic investment
would I need
to create a company like Open?  Hey,
okay?  So I ask this question to
GPT chat.
So,
look, hardware.  Well, look, uh, Nvidia,
sorry, Nvidia,
OpenI has
between 10,000 and 25,000
Nvidia A1 or H1 type GPUs, each of
which costs around 25,000 to
40,000 and has between 10,000 and 25,000 of
these in hardware.
Estimated cost hundreds of millions of
dollars.  Okay.  Microsoft invested more than
1 billion.
Petabyte storage.
Energy grid, mother of God, tens of
megawatts.  I mean, I'd have to go to
Iberdol in Madrid and say, "Look, let's have
a meeting because I need a lot of
electricity. Human resources. Just a
minute, okay? With salaries between
star researchers, okay? Between
150,000 and 300,000 engineers a year
, that is, between 300 and 1,000
employees for a serious phase.
Economic investment. Well, look, I need
an investment in the startup range
between 20 and 50 million dollars, an
intermediate phase between 100 and 300 and an
advanced phase between 1 billion, that
is, over 1 billion dollars.
My project is going to be, I'm going to do an
openi. The answer is no. I
mean, this is not realistic for a
first-year project. Okay, so
let's do something that's realistic.
Identify representative companies,
okay? That said, that said, I,
for example, come here, exercises, I
'm going to, oh, sorry, here  No. I'm going to create
an exercise
here. Intermodular project,
information search, exercises. Okay.
001 and
search for companies, representative companies
MD
and I say, this is what you will have to
do later. I want to
do a project related to AI. I do
n't know yet
what I want to do.
Uh, I want to do something that is viable and
realistic
with the resources available—
wait, this little sign is
bothering me—of those available to
a small or medium-sized
Valencian company.
And first of all,
I need to have a global vision of
the AI ​​business market
,
large agents, uh,
local players.
H services that are being
offered,
opportunities
at the local level that the big ones may not
be covering.
Generalism
versus customization,
okay? I mean, this is what I have to
do, okay? So now
next, tell me
large companies or, well, large,
small, foreign, local, okay?
Tell me which companies you know about
artificial intelligence. I could
ask the GPT chat, okay? But
I'm asking you
very nicely, Deepsic.
Okay, so it turns out that Deep
Sick, I would go for a moment, just a
moment, let's go for it, okay?
Copilot and Grock, okay? Okay,
so let's get a little
idea of ​​the ecosystem
at the moment in which, well, or
Chinese artificial intelligence company has
gained relevance
at the end of 2024 because its algorithm
is more efficient
than Chat GPT or GPT,
okay? And therefore consumes fewer
energy resources
and uses
less powerful hardware than Openai.
Okay, at a given moment, it started the
market a few months ago. Okay, fine.
Copilot.
Copilot is Microsoft's artificial intelligence
integrated
into its products
such as Visual Studio,
GitHub,
and Office, among others.
Okay? What else? Grock. Grock, if
I remember correctly, is the one from X.
It is, if I say something incorrect,
correct me, it is the AI ​​of X.com, Twitter, the
old Twitter,
okay? And uh, let's say under the control of Elon
Musk.
What else? What else is there? Obviously
we have Openai,
which is currently the technological leader
in  Artificial intelligence, the
visible face,
the creators of GPD chat.
Mistral, very good, perfect. Mistral
is a
French and American capital project, which
means that right now it's a
very powerful project
and it places
AI in European territory
thanks to the Spanish, right? Thanks to
the French. Okay, what else are there
? These are probably the
biggest ones, but what it's about is for us to
do a little
research, okay? We can
ask Chat GPT, we can search on
Google, but what I want is to know
what's out there. Before I get into
trouble and start developing and then
realize that what I've
developed is useless because it
already existed, well, before that, it's about getting
a little bit of a position in the market and
knowing what's out there. We're talking about the
big ones.
What about the small ones? I mean,
locally in Valencia, what's there?
Well, I don't know. Okay? And since I don't know, I'm
asking, because
if I'm going to
start a project right now,  At a local level, I
'll need to know a little about the
environment I'm working in. So, at a
local Valencian geographic level
, what
artificial intelligence providers do we find? You'll
say none. I don't know. Let's see.
Let's look at
this Parencian art that develops
artificial intelligence agents for
regulated environments. I did
n't know this, and I need to
know about it. Let's see at a local level. Mai,
look, I'm going to copy this
directly
to investigate it further later.
Let's see, Valentín.
€5 million My. Active
Mirror. Collecting data through
decorative events
to improve user experiences in
fitness.
Ah, well, look, it's interesting. It
's not a principle that I thought to
dedicate the project to, but if I thought to
dedicate the project to all those kinds of
things, well, it's interesting to know that there
's already a company that has made progress in this,
which doesn't mean that I won't
do it, it simply means that I should
be aware that these people have already
started.
Hayster,
automatic image creation and
design. Okay, cool. Quibim, eh, has
medical imaging projects. I don't know, well  I'll
investigate. Now it would be a matter of
taking Quibim and typing Google here and
searching and seeing what Quibim is exactly,
okay? And looking for
more leads, artificial intelligence company
. Oh, careful.
Artificial intelligence for marketing. Big Bro
Sports, okay? With a sports focus,
artificial intelligence.
Audio transformations, voice,
artificial intelligence. Okay,
okay. Now I would have to do a
long and tedious job of going into each and
every one of the web pages. It can be
done with GPT chat, okay? But if we
do it ourselves, it's better to go
into each of the pages, uh, see what
these companies have and get an idea
of ​​the ecosystem. Okay? So,
from here on,
from here on, uh, it's often said that
ignorance
is very bold,
and I'm going to give a meaning, a
sense to this saying that
generally doesn't have it. Uh, this
saying is often used to say that
ignorant people are very careless,
okay? and they always rush into things without thinking.
But what happens?
Rushing into things without thinking sometimes  It's dangerous
because you can waste time.
You can
launch a product onto the market without it being
tested,
or the market already has that product,
and your product, your development, your
project isn't necessary.
However,
overanalyzing
the market, if you don't interpret
the data well,
can make
you back down unnecessarily.
I'm going to ask you something.
What I'm going to ask you may seem like
nonsense, but now you'll see that it
isn't.
Imagine I want to open a bar; it
has nothing to do with IT, it
has nothing to do with
artificial intelligence. Imagine I open a
bar. Imagine I say, of course,
since there are already many bars—
in fact, Spain is the country of
bars—well, of course, why would
I open a bar? Because, surely, since there are
so many bars, people won't come to mine.
What do you think about what I just
said?
Since there are many bars,
people won't come to mine. What do you
think about what I just said? Do you
agree or disagree?  Okay?
In the meantime, I'm going to open
some tea, some tea drink.
Well, of course, fine, correct. Okay, that's what I
'm getting at. Very well. Of course, since
Spain is a country of bars, if you open
one, statistically, someone is going to come in
because people are from bars, people
come into bars. Okay? Then,
indeed, there are times when you
like a bar and you go to that bar, but
when you go somewhere, it's okay
if you don't know that bar, because
you say, "Well, I have to have lunch, I have to have
breakfast.  I'm late, look, a
bar, well, I'll have breakfast there because we
Spaniards are like that, okay?
So what happens?
There's an interpretation that since there are so
many bars, people won't come to mine,
but there's another interpretation that since there
are so many bars,
people have a bar culture.
This is
the glass half empty and this is
the glass half full.
When you analyze the market and see that
there are people who already have the same product
that you are going to offer, right?  When
you find that your product is
already offered, you can interpret it as
something that I want to do
already exists,
so why would I offer it?
But another way of looking at it is if
someone already offers it,
that's because the market demands it.  And
if the market demands it, it may be that
the person offering it isn't
covering the entire market, so there
's room for me.
In the same way,
when you find
that your product is
not yet on the market,
that means that you may be
seeing a need
that no one has covered,
or perhaps it may mean that it has already been
attempted to cover before,
but without success.
Others have tried, but have not
succeeded.  Be careful,
because even if others didn't
succeed, you might not succeed either.
Or where others failed, you
will succeed.  Don't know.
But how can we know all that?
Well, by analyzing the market, that
is, before we get down to
developing, we
have an understanding of the
market we are going to work on.
Look, it gave work in the world of
training, as you know,
obviously.
And the world of training has many,
many details, many folds, many
changes.
and has a lot of world to see.
So, in the same way that the
world of training requires knowledge
of
other worlds,
architecture, construction,
sports, cycling, the "I know what I know," you
know?  Masonry, a
dollar store, what do I know, you know?  Every
business, a dentist, for example, every
business has its own thing, it has a lot of
information that you have to know.
Generally, when someone is going to set up
a project, I tell them, "Do or try to
do a project on a terrain that you
know,
because it's not just about programming."  For
example, one day a student came to me and
said, "I want to do, because I used to work as a
waiter, I want to do a project
reserving tables in a restaurant."  I
said, "Fantastic, because you know about
that and I've never worked as a
waiter."  That thing you sometimes see and you pass by and you
see that they have a screen to mark
things, but I don't know how the
program works or how a room works at the
waiter level.
In that same course there was a student who
was a cook, but not a cook who
cooked at home, but who had
studied cooking.  Okay?  I said,
"Look, if I know little about waiters, I know
nothing about cooks. Okay? I
mean, I know you have a series of
workflows, I know there are different roles
within a
high-end restaurant kitchen, but I don't know what they are or
how they work because I'm really bad at
cooking. So I said, "You
can do that show.  I can't
do that program.  If I'm asked to
do that program, I'll first have
to sit down with a chef and
say, "Explain to me how
this works on the inside so I can
understand what you need."
Because right now I don't understand it,
because it's not that I don't understand it, it
's that I don't know,
but if I have to make software
aimed at the training sector, it
happens that I am a trainer, so I
understand this world.  Okay?
So my recommendation
is that if you know a specific world,
if you know a specific terrain,
try to make the software for that
specific terrain.  Okay?  Well, with that, that
's a little more for this subject today.  I'll
leave this with you, I'll let you
think about it, I'll let you analyze it.
You have until next week, okay?   I'll
ask you again on Thursday.  But
you understand that you'll have until next week to
think a little about what
terrain you'd like to explore when
developing a project.  And from there, you already
know that the first activity I'll
assign you will be to conduct a
market study, both at the macro
and micro levels, of what's
on the market.  so you can get an
idea of ​​which people are offering which
products and therefore what niche there is
for you.  Okay?
Okay, let's take a break between
classes.  Now that we are at the
beginning, since there comes a time when we
cannot go any further, we will
take breaks later on, eh, you will
see how we will go often, often, often, often
, often, that is, we will
go hour, hour, hour, hour, hour, hour and
so on, but now take advantage of the fact that
we are at the beginning and we are taking
5, 10 minute breaks between classes and
later on, well, that
will no longer be like that and we will do it more often.   I'm
not leaving the room.  Okay, I'm staying
here in the living room.